"The Job Done Right"
--------------------

* View Locations[](https://www.certifiedtransmission.com/finder/)

* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Certified Transmission in Omaha. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information** You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

* See what data we have about you, if any.
* Change/correct any data we have about you.
* Have us delete any data we have about you.
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Links** This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at the number(s) listed on our website.**

### Thank You

Certified Transmission thanks you for visiting our website. Our company is dedicated to a superior level of customer service and takes great pride in being recognized as the best transmission remanufacturer in the United States.

Sincerely,  
Peter Fink  
Owner & Founder

### Retail Store Locations

Bellevue  
[1303 Fort Crook Rd. N.  
Bellevue, NE 68005](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=1303+Fort+Crook+Rd.+N.+Bellevue+NE+68005&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

75th and Pacific  
[7516 Pacific Street  
Omaha, NE 68114](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=7516+Pacific+Street+Omaha+NE+68114&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

108th and Maple  
[11005 Emmet Street  
Omaha, NE 68164](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=11005+Emmet+Street+Omaha+NE+68164&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Millard  
[13225 Q Street  
Omaha, NE 68137](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=13225+Q+Street+Omaha+NE+68137&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Lincoln  
[1801 Cornhusker Hwy.  
Lincoln, NE 68521](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=1801+Cornhusker+Hwy.+Lincoln+NE+68521&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Council Bluffs  
[2112 West Broadway  
Council Bluffs, IA 51501](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=2112+West+Broadway+Council+Bluffs+IA+51501&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Overland Park  
[7524 Frontage Road  
Overland Park, KS 66204](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=7524+Frontage+Road+Overland+Park+KS+66204&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Olathe  
[503 East Santa Fe  
Olathe, KS 66061](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=503+East+Santa+Fe+Olathe+KS+66061&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Topeka  
[2081 S. Kansas Avenue  
Topeka, KS 66612](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=2081+S.+Kansas+Avenue+Topeka+KS+66612&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Gladstone  
[5700 North Oak Trafficway  
Gladstone, MO 64118](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=5700+North+Oak+Trafficway+Gladstone+MO+64118&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Grandview  
[12908 South 71 Hwy.  
Grandview, MO 64030](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=12908+South+71+Hwy.+Grandview+MO+64030&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Independence  
[820 West 23rd St S  
Independence, MO 64055](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=820+West+23rd+St+S+Independence+MO+64055&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Liberty  
[569 North Mo Hwy. 291  
Liberty, MO 64068](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=569+North+Mo+Hwy.+291+Liberty+MO+64068&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

Blue Springs  
[527 MO-7  
Blue Springs, MO 64014](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=527+MO-7+Blue+Springs+MO+64014&oe=utf-8&gl=us&z=7)  

#### Follow Us

#### We Accept

© 2021  
Certified Transmission.  
All Rights Reserved.  
Website by:
